easycumeasyblow.com 2013-06-29

# Privacy Policy - EasyCumEasyBlow.com

General

While visiting a **Twin Stones Entertainment** ("Twin Stones Ent.") owned site, we may ask you to register and/or provide information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information") for purposes of interacting with our site, including, for example, when you ask for information, send feedback, or download material. Twin Stones Ent. intends to give you as much control as possible over your Personal Information. If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information via a Twin Stones Ent. owned site, it is our intent to let you know how we will use your Personal Information. Twin Stones Ent. uses your Personal Information to help you quickly find our services or information on the site. We track the domains from which this site is visited and use that data to analyze for trends and statistics, and then discard it. If you choose not to have your Personal Information used as a basis for further contact with you by Twin Stones Ent. or one of its business partners, you may "opt out". If you choose not to give us your Personal Information, you can still use most of this site. You merely will not be able to access areas that require registration. Additionally, if you do not want Twin Stones Ent. to send you e-mail or postal mail regarding easycumeasyblow.com or its services, you may "opt out" at the time you give us your Personal Information. The following information is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disseminate and safeguard the information you provide to us while accessing and using our Site. By accessing and using our Site, you signify your consent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not access or use our Site. As provided below, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, add or remove portions of this policy at any time by posting such changes to this page. Such changes will be effective upon posting. We collect personal information that you choose to provide voluntarily when purchasing download materials or services from a Twin Stones Ent. owned site. This information includes your email address and a password when you when purchase download materials or services from a Twin Stones Ent. owned site. 

The Way We Use and Whom We Share Your Personal Information With

We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We may share aggregated demographic and statistical information with our partners or sponsors. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

How We Protect Your Personal Information

We use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the information you have provided to us from unauthorized access by using encryption and other security measures. 

Third Party Billing Companies

The third party billing companies which collect your payment for using our services collect personal and billing information that we have access to but do not store. You acknowledge and agree that we do not have any responsibility for the collection, maintenance or safeguarding of the privacy of any such personal or billing information provided to such third party billing companies and that such responsibility is solely between you and the third party billing company. We encourage you to examine and determine your satisfaction with the policies of such third party billing companies prior to using them. 

Links to Other Materials

If any link is offered connecting to a third party website, it is as an accommodation to the respective third party site owner and without charge. Sites linked to and from this site are not necessarily under the control of Twin Stones Ent. and Twin Stones Ent. shall have no responsibilities or liabilities whatsoever for the content or privacy practices of any such linked site or any link or linking program at any time. Twin Stones Ent. does not necessarily endorse companies (or related products or services) to or from which this site is linked. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to this site, you do so entirely at your own risk. Twin Stones Ent. hereby disclaims any rights to trademarks, service marks, trade names, logos, copyrights, patents, domain names or other intellectual property interests of third parties. 

Cookies

There is a technology called "cookies" which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a website. A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. Some Twin Stones Ent. site pages may use cookies so that we may better serve you when you return to our site. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. 

Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such changes on this page. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective upon posting such changes. If you access or use a Twin Stones Ent. owned site, you are required to periodically check our Privacy Policy for any changes. If you continue to access or use a Twin Stones Ent. owned site after we have changed our Privacy Policy, you manifest your assent to the changes to our Privacy Policy. 

How to Contact Twin Stones Entertainment

If you have comments or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [info@twinstones.com](mailto:info@twinstones.com). 

| 

|  |  MY CART |    
---|---|---  

0 Movie \+ 0 Free Movie

Add 3 movies and  
GET 3 FREE!
